Mahadi Hasan

Narail District, Khulna, Bangladesh



mahadi.dev.pm@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mahadi-hasan-99080a237

Summary

I am a Full Stack Web developer with more than 3 years of experience in this field. I have been working in a freelance marketplace. I started my coding/career when I was 14. Now I am 18. I am a young professional passionate about web development and design. My mission is to help you grow your business

Experience

ဟု Senior Web Developer

Upwork

Jan 2023 - Present (1 month)

I recently started working on Upwork on 1st Jan 2023.

Freelance Web Developer

Freelancer.com

Jan 2020 - Present (3 years 1 month)

I have been working on this freelance marketplace since 2020. I started my career when I was 14. I got my first account suspended to use my fake identity. I used fake identity for my age.

fi Web Developer

Fiverr

Apr 2020 - Dec 2022 (2 years 9 months)

I was working as a Web Developer on fiverr.com I stopped working in this site 12 months ago.

Education

Dighalia Ideal Secondary School

High School Diploma, Business/Commerce, General

Jan 2017 - Apr 2033

I have been studying at Business line but I feel good while I do coding.

Skills

Adobe Premiere Pro • Adobe Photoshop • jQuery • Tailwind CSS • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5 • MySQL • TypeScript • PHP • JavaScript